http://www.barkeranimation.com/privacy-policy/?___SID=j2kdguorv27jdbp9g1ivr8fep2U

Barker Animation Art Galleries
Search:
Search
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare
You have no items to compare.
Home
Artist ARCYRomero BrittoJames ColemanHeather (Theurer) EdwardsTom EverhartCharles FazzinoChuck JonesThomas Kinkade StudiosBill MelendezTim RogersonAlex RossDr. Seuss (Theodor Geisel)Myron WaldmanDavid WillardsonBrowse All ArtistsStudio Bill Melendez Productions, Inc.Clampett StudiosDC ComicsDisneyDisney / PixarDr. Seuss Enterprises, L.P.Hanna-BarberaKing Features SyndicateLinda Jones EnterprisesLucasfilm Ltd.Marvel ComicsUniversal StudiosWarner Bros.Browse All StudiosCharacter BatmanBelleBetty BoopBugs BunnyDarth VaderDoctor Strange (Stephen Vincent Strange, M.D.)GrinchMickey MouseMinnie MousePopeyeScooby-DooSnoopyBrowse All CharactersTheme AvengersBaseballBlack PantherDentistDisney PrincessesDoctorFootballFrozenJudaicLawyerPEANUTSRomanceScooby-Doo and the GangStar WarsThe Lion KingBrowse All ThemesSignature Marc DavisBob DoucetteDerek JeterOllie JohnstonChuck JonesMichael JordanWard KimballStan LeeJohn Romita Jr.Iwao TakamotoFrank ThomasMyron WaldmanBrowse All Signatures
Locations
It's More Than A Store, It's An Experience...
Visit one of our two Connecticut locations today!
Cheshire, CT
Since opening in 1994, more than 14,000 collectors have proudly displayed artwork purchased from our Cheshire Gallery in their homes and offices.
More details...
Mashantucket, CT
Located at the Tanger Outlets in Foxwoods Resort and Casino, our Mashantucket Gallery opened in 2016.
More details...
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This notice discloses the privacy practices for BarkerAnimation.com, and applies solely to information collected by this website.
It will notify you of the following:
- What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.- What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.- The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.- How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future communication from us at any time. You can do the following at any time through your Star Club account or by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
- See what data we have about you, if any.- Change/correct any data we have about you.- Have us delete any data we have about you.- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, order fulfillment or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (203) 272-2357 or via email at fun@barkeranimation.com.
Information
About Us
FAQ
Art 101
Locations
Blog
Web
Advanced Search
Loading...
